Nima Razi

Myllykatu 11 | 65100 Vaasa | (+358) 41 478 6217 | nima.razi@hotmail.com

PROFILE

I graduated with bachelors in Business Information Technology from Vaasa University of Applied Sciences in 2022 and I'm applying for part-time or fixed-term positions in the field of IT. I've worked as a software developer with APS.NET- & REST.API-projects together with IT-support tasks. My programming tasks mainly consisted of front-end development. My career objectives include improving in IT-support and front-end development.

EXPERIENCE

05/2023 - 10/2023 | Software Developer, Cash-In Consulting Oy (ASP.NET, Oracle SQL & IT-support)

01/2022 - 08/2022 | Software Developer, Pilvilampi Software Oy (REST.API, SharePoint & Helpdesk)

06/2019 - 08/2019 | Cleaner, Kartanon Puhtauspalvelut Oy

05/2018 - 08/2018 | Cleaner, Kartanon Puhtauspalvelut Oy

11/2017 | Greenhouse worker, Wääksyn Puutarha Oy

06/2016 - 08/2016 | Paper deliverer, Tampereen Ykkösjakelut Oy

EDUCATION

08/2018 - 12/2022 | Bachelor of Business Information Technology, Vaasa University of Applied Sciences 08/2012 - 12/2016 | Matriculation examination, Tampere High School of Technology

LANGUAGES

finnish – excellent english – excellent swedish - weak kurdish - weak farsi – native language

IT-EXPERIENCE

Microsoft 365: Word, PowerPoint, Excel, Access, SharePoint & Power BI 3ds Max, DaVinci Resolve, Oracle VM VirtualBox & Adobe XD WordPress & Piranha CMS
Oracle SQL, MariaDB & Microsoft SQL Server
HTML, CSS & JavaScript (Bootstrap)

OTHERS

B-drivers license

Sports Scolarship & (B2) english | Tampere High School of Technology

Conscription Service, Pori Brigade 2017

LinkedIn

GitHub